# STEN MAYUNGA

## DEVELOPER

## SUMMARY

I am a highly analytical and motivated individual, with extensive experience in developing dynamic websites and software. My strength are in problem solving, communication and working on my own initiative as a self taught developer. I am passionate of my new career in development and dedicated to continuous learning. I have completed numerous paid and unpaid real-world projects to showcase my competent use of front and back-end technologies, most of which can be found on my developer website:

https://www.stentechdev.com.

I am a confident speaker with over a decade of public speaking experience and work very well in a team.

## **CONTACT**

Dartford, Kent

+447861638448

stentechdev@gmail.com

stentechdev.com

linkedin.com/in/stentechdev

### **EDUCATION**

**London App Brewery**Full Stack Bootcamp

University of Kent BSc (Hons)



Visit my portfolio website:

stentechdev.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Developer, Freelance - 2014-Present

I have been designing and creating website as a hobby and freelance web developer on and off since 2014. I've used platform such as Wix, Shopify and Wordpress and have become familiar with Liquid and PHP as a result. My preferred programming language is JavaScript which I am currently mastering. I am constantly learning and willing to adapt my technologies to best suit the projects I work on.

#### Full Stack Developer, London App Brewery — 2021-2022

During my time studying and working on project at the London App Brewery bootcamp, I learn an extensive list of technologies and tools which included: JS ES6, JQuery, Node.js, APIs, SQL, React.js just to name a few as well as Backend and Front-End Web Development. At the end of the bootcamp, I completed over 25 websites, some of which can be found on my developer website.

#### Technical Support Specialist, Bose Corporation — 2020-2021

I worked with the US customer base by providing them with product troubleshooting and guiding customers to solve any problem that may have arisen with their Bose products or accounts. I built a knowledge of all the products suite available and the software used to run the products. Problem solving and persistence was key in this role which had a direct correlation to customer satisfaction.

#### **Skills**

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, JS ES6, DOM Manipulation, JQuery, Bash Command Line, Git, GitHub, Version Control, Node.js, NPM, Express.js, EJS, REST, APIs, Databases, SQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, Authentication, Firebase, React.js, React Hooks, Deployment with GitHub Pages, Heroic and MongoDB Atlas